BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8) 6178/008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series XXIII: Code #92, Public Administration
  - Code no.811391: Pittsburgh, City of and Pittsburgh Joint Collective Bargaining Committee, 1979-2002 (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Code no.811500: DC Department of Recreation and American Federation of Government Employees, 1978-1980 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Code no.811714: Phoenix, City of and State, County and Municipal Employees, 1980-1992 (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Code no.811824: Providence, City of and Laborers' International Union of North America, 1982-1991 (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - Code no.811825: Los Angeles, City of and Engineers and Architects Association, 1985-1997 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Code no.811826: Los Angeles, City of and United Firemen of Los Angeles, 1987-1992 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Code no.811827: Los Angeles, City of and State, County and Municipal Employees, 1983-1988 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Code no.811832: Phoenix, City of (police) and Phoenix Law Enforcement Association, 1983-1992 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Code no.811836: New York City Police Department (detectives) and Detectives' Endowment Association, 1982-1992 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Code no.811838: New York City Police Department (sergeants) and Sergeants Benevolent Association, 1982-1990 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Code no.6789: Food Fair and UFCW, 1972-1999 (Box 158, Folder 9)
  - Code no.811839: New York City Police Department (patrolmen) and Police Benevolent Association, 1984-1987 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Code no.811845: District of Columbia (police) and Fraternal Order of Police, 1988-1995 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Code no.811846: Los Angeles Department of Power and Water and IBEW, 1988-2000 (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - Code no.811861: Seattle, City of and International Association of Fire Fighters, 1992-1994 (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - Code no.811868: Chicago, City of and Fraternal Order of Police, 1989-1991 (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - Code no.811869: San Antonio, City of and International Association of Fire Fighters, 1988-1992 (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - Code no.811876: New York City Police Department (police lieutenants) and BAC, 1992-1995 (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - Code no.820009: Milwaukee County and State, County and Municipal Employees, 1967-1988 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Code no.820048: Dade County (general classified) and State, County and Municipal Employees, 1980-1988 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Code no.820149: Suffolk County and CSEA, 1977-1991 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Code no.820210: San Diego County and San Diego County Employees Association, 1977-1994 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Code no.820211: Riverside County and Professional Unit, 1980-1993 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Code no.820215: Los Angeles County and Los Angeles County Employees Association, 1977-1991 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Code no.820216: Los Angeles County and Service Employees International Union, 1989-1991 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Code no.820218: Los Angeles County and Service Employees International Union, 1987-1993 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Code no.820223: Los Angeles, City of and Engineers and Architects Association, 1985-1997 (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - Code no.820251: Burlington County, Board of Freeholders and CWA, 1977-1994 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Code no.820265: Westmoreland County and Service Employees International Union, 1980-1988 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Code no.820289: Rensselaer County and CSEA, 1978-1993 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Code no.820344: Westchester County and CSEA, 1978-1987 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Code no.820348: Erie County and CSEA, 1975-1987 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Code no.820349: Erie County and State, County and Municipal Employees, 1979-1987 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Code no.820351: Saratoga County and CSEA, 1979-1987 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Code no.820383: Ulster County and State, County and Municipal Employees, 1977-1988 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Code no.820389: Broome County and CSEA, 1991-1991 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Code no.820456: County of Hennepin and State, County and Municipal Employees, 1988-1997 (Box 123, Folder 10)
    1988-1991, 1996-1997
  - Code no.820486: Los Angeles County (office & clerical unit 111) and Service Employees International Union, 1983- 1992 (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - Code no.820489: Dade County Florida and Dade County Association of Fire Fighters, 1978-1999 (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - Code no.820496: Los Angeles County (clerical supervisors Unit 112) and Service Employees International Union, 1979-1989 (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - Code no.820541: Wayne County, Michigan and State, County and Municipal Employees, 1982-1998 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Code no.820578: Sonoma, County of and Sonoma County Organization of Public Employees, 1976-1989 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Code no.820635: Monterey, County of and Service Employees Union, 1981-1993 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Code no.820670: Riverside County and Public Employees Association of Riverside County, 1980-1991 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Code no.820696: San Joaquin County and San Joaquin County Employees Association, 1981-1989 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Code no.820810: Montgomery County Government and UFCW, 1987-1997 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Code no.830473: Shasta County and Laborers' International Union of North America, 1997-2002 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Code no.830838: State of California Bargaining Unit 15 and Service Employees International Union, 1992-1995 (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Code no.830839: State of California Bargaining Unit 4 and Service Employees International Union, 1992-1995 (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Code no.840037: Ramsey County and State, County and Municipal Employees, 1994-1999 (Box 128, Folder 8)
  - Code no.840039: Columbus, City of and Columbus Municipal Association of Government Employees, 1994-1999 (Box 128, Folder 9)
  - Code no.800009: Pennsylvania, Commonwealth of and State, County and Municipal Employees, 1976-1988 (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Code no.800077: Wisconsin, State of and State, County and Municipal Employees, 1979-1989 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Code no.800097: Minnesota, State of and State, County and Municipal Employees, 1979-1989 (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Code no.800122: Massachusetts, Commonwealth of and Maintenance Trades Council, 1977-1983 (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - Code no.800155: Pennsylvania, Commonwealth of and State, County and Municipal Employees, 1978-1988 (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Code no.800199: Ohio, State of and CSEA, 1978-1992 (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Code no.800219: Hawaii, State of and United Public Workers, 1979-1987 (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - Code no.800242: Hawaii Department of Civil Service and Hawaiian Government Employees Association, 1981-1987 (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - Code no.800245: Hawaii, State of and United Public Workers, 1977-1987 (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - Code no.800246: Hawaii, State of and Hawaii Government Employees Association, 1981-1985 (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - Code no.800248: Hawaii, State of and State, County and Municipal Employees, 1981-1987 (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - Code no.800249: Hawaii, State of and Hawaii Fire Fighters Association, 1979-1989 (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Code no.800340: Iowa, State of and AFSCME, 1981-1989 (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - Code no.800346: Michigan, State of and Michigan Corrections Organization, 1983-1987 (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - Code no.800347: Vermont, State of and Vermont State Employees' Association, 1988-1990 (Box 130, Folder 12)
  - Code no.800413: Iowa, State of and State, County and Municipal Employees, 1981-1989 (Box 130, Folder 13)
  - Code no.810084: Baltimore, City of and Classified Municipal Employees Association, 1978-1990 (Box 130, Folder 14)
  - Code no.810287: Hartford, City of and AFL-CIO, 1979-1996 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Code no.810492: Boston (firefighters) and International Association of Fire Fighters, 1977-1987 (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Code no.810612: Milwaukee, City of and International Association of Fire Fighters, 1977-1987 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Code no.810643: Portland, City of and District Council of Trade Unions, 1978-1987 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Code no.810646: Jacksonville, City of and State, County and Municipal Employees, 1980-1988 (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - Code no.811146: Dayton, City of and State, County and Municipal Employees, 1979-1988 (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - Code no.811248: Trenton, City of and State, County and Municipal Employees, 1977-1989 (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - Code no.811331: Albuquerque, City of and State, County and Municipal Employees, 1981-1988 (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - Code no.811425: Glendale, City of and Glendale City Employees' Association, 1976-1987 (Box 131, Folder 11)
  - Code no.811490: Tampa, City of and Amalgamated Transit Union, 1979-1990 (Box 131, Folder 12)
  - Code no.811779: Cincinnati, City of and Fraternal Order of Police, 1978-1986 (Box 131, Folder 13)
  - Code no.820216: Los Angeles County Board of Supervisors (custodial services) and Service Employees International Union, 1979- 1989 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Code no.820219: Los Angeles County Board of Supervisors and Service Employees International Union, 1977-1989 (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - Code no.820287: Nashville & Davidson City Metro Government and Service Employees International Union, 1984- 1985 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Code no.820350: Chautauqua County and CSEA, 1974-1989 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - Code no.820456: Hennepin MN, County of and State, County and Municipal Employees, 1978-1987 (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Code no.820535: Rockland NY, County of and Rockland County CSEA, 1983-1988 (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Code no.820537: Ventura, County of and Public Employees Association, 1979-1988 (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - Code no.820621: Genesee County and State, County and Municipal Employees, 1985-1989 (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - Code no.820698: San Joaquin CA, City of (off, tech, clerical) and San Jose Conservation Corps, 1983-1989 (Box 132, Folder 12)
  - Code no.820793: Alameda, County of and Service Employees International Union, 1983-1989 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Code no.820795: Sacramento, County of (office-technical unit) and Sacramento County Employees, 1983-1988 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Code no.820842: Buffalo, City of (Police) and Buffalo Police Benevolent Association, 1986-1988 (Box 135, Folder 3)